adcomarketing.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy for Adco Marketing - Promotional Items & Promotional Products

### **Adco Marketing Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online and internal information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Adco Marketing website (www.adcomarketing.com). Some pages are secure while email requests and simple information requests have the same security as a typical email message.  On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive material. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

* Name

* Address

* Email Address

* Phone Number

* Fax Number

* Company Name

* Shipper * information

* (etc)

* On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a product online and want it sent directly to another recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name

* Address

* Email Address

* Phone Number

* (etc)

We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and site statistics.

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order for our promotional items, promotional products and other items offered on our site only to complete that order. We do not share information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

When an Quote Request, Information Request, or other contact form is used, you may receive an email order acknowledgement. ** Please do not email us credit card number information, as email is not encrypted or secure.** If you do not feel comfortable entering your credit card information over the internet, please call **1-888-332-ADCO or 415-927-2881** and one of our representatives will be happy to help you.

When you register with our website you will receive updates on our new products and services. If you wish to be removed from this list, please send an email to [sales@adcomarketing.com](mailto:sales@adcomarketing.com "Privacy Policy") .

You may also receive periodic mailings from Adco Marketing (i.e. catalogs, flyers). If you wish to be removed from this mailing list, please send an email to [sales@adcomarketing.com](mailto:sales@adcomarketing.com "Privacy Policy") .

We do not share your phone number with outside parties. Your phone number will be used to contact you regarding order information. Occasionally, we may contact you via phone to inform you of new products and special deals we are offering. If you do not wish to receive this information by phone, please contact [sales@adcomarketing.com](mailto:sales@adcomarketing.com "Privacy Policy") .

We do not share your email address with any outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at **1-888-332-ADCO** or send us an email at [sales@adcomarketing.com](mailto:sales@adcomarketing.com "Privacy Policy") .  Our mailing address is:

Adco Marketing  
300 Tamal Plaza  
Suite 220  
Corte Madera, CA 94925

By Visiting [www.adcomarketing.com](http://www.adcomarketing.com/ "Adco Marketing Promotional Items Home Page"), you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.

This Privacy Policy has been in effect since 3/25/2010
